export const navData = [
  { name: 'About', href: 'about-us' },
  { name: 'How to', href: 'how' },
  { name: 'Faqs', href: 'faqs' },
];

export const accordions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: 'What is a professional traffic permit?',
    answer: 'Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet consectetur, adipisicing elit. Aut, voluptatum. Voluptatem, fugiat?',
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: 'How to check the traffic condition?',
    answer: 'Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet consectetur, adipisicing elit. Aut, voluptatum.',
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: 'What are the requirements for a professional traffic permit?',
    answer: 'Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet consectetur, adipisicing elit. Aut, voluptatum. Voluptatem, fugiat?',
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: 'Are there professional traffic permit training courses at a distance?',
    answer: 'Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet consectetur, adipisicing elit. Aut, voluptatum.',
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: 'When is a professional traffic permit needed?',
    answer: 'Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet consectetur, adipisicing elit. Aut, voluptatum. Voluptatem, fugiat?',
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: 'Where to look for a traffic permit?',
    answer: 'Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet consectetur, adipisicing elit. Aut, voluptatum.',
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: 'Are there differences between a traffic permit and a professional traffic permit?',
    answer: 'Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet consectetur, adipisicing elit. Aut, voluptatum. Voluptatem, fugiat?',
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: 'How much does a commercial traffic permit cost for goods?',
    answer: 'Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet consectetur, adipisicing elit. Aut, voluptatum.',
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: 'How to plug in for the traffic permit test?',
    answer: 'Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet consectetur, adipisicing elit. Aut, voluptatum. Voluptatem, fugiat?',
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: 'How is the sample for a professional traffic permit booked?',
    answer: 'Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet consectetur, adipisicing elit. Aut, voluptatum.',
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: 'What is a professional traffic permit?',
    answer: 'Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet consectetur, adipisicing elit. Aut, voluptatum. Voluptatem, fugiat?',
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: 'How to check the traffic condition?',
    answer: 'Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet consectetur, adipisicing elit. Aut, voluptatum.',
  },
];
